bookingbuddy.eu 2016-05-18

# BookingBuddy privacy policy

_This Privacy Policy was last changed August 17, 2009._

## Overview

Welcome to BookingBuddy.co.uk ("BookingBuddy"). The following Privacy Policy explains how BookingBuddy gathers and uses information that is provided by our customers.

## What information we collect from you

_In General_. We do not currently collect information that can identify you ("personal information"), such as your email address or telephone number, but plan to do so in the near future. When we make this change, we will post an updated privacy policy to describe what personal information will be collected and how it will be used. Please review our current privacy policy periodically.

_Automatic Information_. We automatically collect some information about your computer when you visit BookingBuddy. For example, we will collect your IP address, and information relating to your Web browser software (such as Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) and referring Web site. We also may collect information about your online activity, such as trips viewed. One of our goals in collecting this information is to help customize your user experience. We do not use this information to identify you.

_Cookies and Other Web Technologies_. When you visit BookingBuddy, we may assign your computer a "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file). You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies from BookingBuddy, you may not be able to access many of the travel tools offered by BookingBuddy.

_Information Collected by Third-Party Advertising Companies_. Third-party advertisers, such as those we use to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet, may use cookies and other technologies (such as Web beacons or single-pixel GIFS) for several purposes, including: to measure the effectiveness of their ads; to analyze, modify, and personalize advertising content on BookingBuddy and other sites; and to provide ads about goods and services we hope will be of interest to you. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features third-party advertising companies may use, and the information practices of these advertisers are not covered by this Privacy Policy. You can find out more about third-party advertisers and explore the option of not having this information collected by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

_Information Collected Through Web Analytics_. BookingBuddy uses a Web analytics company to track and generate reports on visitor use of our site. We use the Web analytics company to analyze visitor activity so that we may better understand how visitors make use of BookingBuddy, and so that we may better tailor content to meet our visitors' needs. This data may include anonymized, individual visitor click behavior. No personally identifiable information is obtained or shared with the Web analytics company. Although our Web analytics company logs the information coming from BookingBuddy on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. Visitors who wish to opt-out of this Web site analysis tool may do so by clicking [here](http://www.omniture.com/privacy/optout.html).

## How we use this information

BookingBuddy uses information we collect for the following general purposes: to measure interest in and improve our products, services, and Web site; to resolve disputes or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

Please review "Your choices with respect to the collection and use of your information" below.

## E-mail Subscriptions, E-mail Communications and Newsletters

If you chose to receive communications from BookingBuddy.co.uk about special promotions when registering as a BookingBuddy.co.uk member, we may use your email address to send you communications about surveys, contests, sweepstakes, promotions, flight specials, deals or other travel news and opportunities on BookingBuddy.co.uk and its marketing partners. If you choose to receive our Newsletters, you may receive communications such as "This Just In", "TripReminder" and periodic announcements about changes to our features at your email address. You can discontinue your subscription to BookingBuddy.co.uk promotional email services at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the email received or by going to BookingBuddy.co.uk and clicking on the Change Subscriptions link at the bottom of the page. You can also unsubscribe to e-mail communications at any time by replying to the email with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line.

## With whom we share this information

BookingBuddy may share the information it collects with the following entities:

  * Third-party vendors who provide services or functions on our behalf, including package delivery, business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution of surveys or sweepstakes programs, and fraud prevention. These companies have access to information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use the information for any other purpose.
  * Business partners who may offer products or services through our site. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service you have requested because their name will be listed. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners and recommend you evaluate their practices before deciding to provide them with any personal information.
  * Companies within the Expedia family. BookingBuddy is a member of the Expedia corporate family. We may share information with our U.S. corporate affiliates, including Hotels.com, TripAdvisor, Hotwire, and Classic Vacations, as well as international corporate affiliates such as Expedia.co.uk, TripAdvisor.co.uk, and Expedia.de. To the extent that our corporate affiliates have access to your information, they will follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

We also may share your information:

  * In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
  * When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of BookingBuddy, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Service and other agreements.
  * In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.

  * We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors a Web site receives or what are the most popular vacation destinations. This information does not contain any personal information and is used to develop content and services we hope you will find of interest.

## How we protect your information

We want you to feel confident about using BookingBuddy to plan and purchase your travel. While no Web site can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the information you provide to us.

## Children's privacy

BookingBuddy does not knowingly collect, maintain or use personal information about children under age 13.

## External Links

BookingBuddy.co.uk links you to other Web sites. Please note that those Web sites do not operate under this Privacy Policy, and we are not responsible for their practices. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other Web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

BookingBuddy may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by placing a notice on our Web site.

## How you can contact us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [privacy@bookingbuddy.co.uk](mailto:privacy@bookingbuddy.co.uk), or mail us at:

Smarter Travel Media LLC   
Attn: BookingBuddy.co.uk   
226 Causeway Street, Third Floor   
Boston, MA 02114, USA

This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 17, 2009.
